Serhii Mohylnyi

Junior QA Manual

seruyyodo@gmail.com



+380931225089



https://www.facebook.com/serhii.mogilny?ref=bookma

Summary -

(LANGUAGES)

- English Threshold Intermediate.
- Russian Native.
- Ukrainian Native.

Professional Skills -

(+)Bug Reports (Jira, Redmine, Mantis, Bugzilla - Bug Tracking Systems)

(+)Test Cases (Test Link, TestRail - Test Management Systems [Management of tests, test plans, test runs]): Test Data, Test Actions, Test Results

(+)HTML/CSS/SQL

(++)Test documentation -Check list, test

(+)JSON/XML/IDEA

(+)Java + Automation -Basic knowledge Selemium WebDriver

(+)Performance testing with Apache JMeter /SoapUI

(++)Windows/Linux

Work experience -

CentralBar

Restaurant Worker Su-cheff

01/2017 - 08/2020

- Assisting the executive chef with meal planning.
- Keeping tabs on kitchen supplies and ingredients when it comes time to prepare the meals.
- Making sure the kitchen is up to sanitation standards in time for daily service.
- Scheduling the other kitchen staff and making sure they arrive on time, and filling in personally if someone calls in sick or is late.

SteakHouse

Restaurant Worker Cook

06/2016 - 12/2018

- Prepared cooking supplies, ingredients and workstations during opening and closing procedures to maximize efficiency.
- Fried, grilled and baked foods such as [Meat], [Vegetable] and [Others].
- Prepared identical dishes numerous times daily with consistent care, attention to detail and quality.

Education —

Odessa Higher Professional School Of Marine Tourism Services

Ship's Cook, Ship's Waiter

2012 - 2014

Secondary School Number 11

No Degree

2001 - 2012

Certificates

2020 DataArt Online Summer Internship Program

Expertise areas include:

1. Tech stack: .Net, Java, JS, CSS, HTML.

2. Testing: QA, Mobile Testing.

3. DevOps, InfoSec, UI/UX Design, ML, AI. 4. Communications: English for IT, soft skills.

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0/?tab=rm#starred?projector=1

2020 Computer School Hillel

QA Manual Course in Hillel Computer School https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/68572003/en

About -

Want learn new profession

All my life i have worked in the restaurant scope, and all this years what i spend i understand i was not happy in this profession, but i always do my best for make it better, and now the moment has come when i want to see myself in IT profession as I originally wanted for a long time.

Additional information

Military obligation status

Unsuitable in peacetime.

Professional interests

Reading professional books and Web-sources (YouTube, forums.etc.)Learning English